What's the hardest thing about love?
People have asked that question for a long, long time.
Oh, Virgos will have super bad luck this month.
Tons of problems.
You should be careful.
I heard keeping crystals will ward off evil.
After class, we should go and buy a bunch.
Aww, looks like Capricorns will meet their soulmate this month.
Okay, who's a goat?
Oh, Sue N, isn't your birthday January 2nd?
Love is in the air.
Some people think the hardest part is accepting your destiny.
Others say it's finding the courage to confess your love.
Excuse me.
Hmm?
Will you be my girlfriend?
Huh?
Ah, excuse me.
Hmm?
Ah, will you be my girlfriend?
Huh?
But for me, the problem is something else, a roadblock most people will never have to
face.
It didn't take too long to realize something has changed in the back of my mind.
Your eyes, there ain't nowhere left to hide behind.
Time no longer flew like it was when the flash froze everything before.
Without you, I don't know if I could take this road.
And I'm about to lose my mind.
Every minute that I'm down back in time.
Every single day, it's just three wines.
Some physical pain in this side drive.
All the hardest and the smiles never faded.
I know you'll be by my side when we make it.
Come back from the dead.
Back in time.
Die back in time.
Now, wheelbarrow!
This phone's crap and the network's lagging.
Plus the update ruined my fighter.
Likely excuses.
Face it, you've got no game.
Next player's up.
It's all yours.
Good luck.
Don't lose, or we have to help her.
This will be child's play.
Hmm.
Ah!
The hell!
You didn't even touch her!
At least I got in a few good punches!
Sorry, you're both losers.
I don't hit girls.
I won the bet, but it doesn't feel like a win.
Try not to screw up this next mission, okay?
Start talking.
What's up?
You've piqued my interest.
Our client's in love with a woman from a martial arts family.
He's confessed his love repeatedly.
Problem is, her dad's a hand-to-hand master.
He'll only approve a marriage if the groom confessed him.
They've also never accepted a non-fighter into the family.
We've also captured a non-fighter into the family.
What about a tribe?
Our guys fought over and over again.
and failed each time.
That's because Big Bad Dad has unique skills,
some secret technique.
The client has no idea how to beat us.
Analyze the father's moves so our client can win and get married.
Hey, can't you just look at a pic and figure them out?
Hmm. I doubt it.
Here. This photo was taken before one of the fights.
Huh. That's sad.
They definitely look like they're in love with each other.
Solve this. And quickly.
He's running out of time.
Come on, man. Stare at the picture and see how the Master fights.
That would save us like so much work.
His skills are secret.
I need you to visit the scene and act as my eyes.
Fine. I'll go.
We lost.
Fair and square.
You ready?
Dive.
An engagement pick before my big win.
Very funny.
My dad is so stubborn.
He's never gonna go easy on you.
I trained hard this year.
Now I've got my own secret skills.
Just wait.
You'll see him soon.
You think you're gonna win every time you fight.
How's that working out for you?
Yeah.
Remember the first time you paid a visit?
We'll see you soon.
We've not accepted an outsider in many generations.
Your efforts are wasted.
Leave this mountain.
What do people say?
Oh, no!
I've come to marry you!
What are you laughing for?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Help him.
Take him into the house.
Stop that, you idiot.
Oh, man, that was hilarious.
I bit it so hard.
Don't shout this time, all right?
But I want to.
Absolutely not!
Maybe you're forgetting what you told me first.
I've still got the evidence.
Why don't you throw that antique in the trash?
Here, give it to me!
Look at you blushing.
It's so cute.
Moron!
Stop adding your own lines.
Suen, there's something that I have to tell you.
Dad's student asked for my hand in marriage.
And did your father say yes?
Who cares?
I didn't.
It's my hand to give and no one else's.
Either way, we both have a mountain to climb.
Don't be late, okay?
Now I get it.
He's running out of time.
Be quick.
Stay smart.
You understand how this power works.
The same photo can't be used twice.
This is our only chance.
I have to climb up the mountain on foot?
The chill link picked us to torture me!
You're walking too slow.
It's two hours to their home.
Don't kick a man while he's down.
Why am I always the one who suffers?
Hello?
Hey, Lou, are you listening?
Are you there yet?
Almost at the top.
Run next.
Wait.
You're early.
Hang tight.
What futile trick does he hope to use against me this time?
Now you're good.
Shout like your life depends on it.
Uyung!
I've come to marry you!
It's the same every year.
Can't you think of something more creative?
This time I'm going to defeat you.
Firstly, you weren't raised in martial arts,
and amateurs aren't welcome in my home.
Secondly, you're younger than my daughter.
I'll never accept this pairing.
Left palm out, right hand back.
Stand tall.
Can you not follow directions?
Reverse it!
Can't even hold a simple stance.
You're hopeless!
Quick, deflect with your left hand.
Have you never been in a fight before?
Why are you moving so slow?
Don't sit there, on your feet!
Careful, he's going high.
Duck!
Plant your right foot.
Limit his movements.
Center yourself!
Shut up!
You're giving me a headache!
Please, you need my help to do this.
As if.
Just sit back and watch.
I'll show you what I'm capable of.
Your movement's like basic economy.
It's obvious that your training is subpar.
Old man, you'll take that back when I've beaten you.
Shall we?
You're disrespectful, little brat!
What's this technique he's using?
He's predicting your father's attacks.
Don't go overboard.
Take a few hits, too.
You taught me?
Special move?
Snatch the club!
What just happened?
Was that the secret move?
The one our client could never beat?
Again, I need a better view.
I've been trying to learn this move for the past decade.
I love her.
Please, Master, approve our marriage.
So, you've finally gathered the courage.
You must know what you ask.
Show me you deserve her hand.
It's no use.
I can't figure out that punch.
And everything hurts.
I think I might pass out.
Hands have gotten numb.
This must be the end.
It's not over yet.
You're kidding.
I can barely move this body.
No way does he keep fighting.
He gets up.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I'm seriously at my limit.
How did he find the strength to stand up again?
Please, call the fight off.
I just won't marry anyone, ever.
How's it going?
You guys figure out the Master's trick?
So, that bad, huh?
A little complicated for you guys?
He's too fast.
No way to see it.
We failed.
Gotcha.
No biggie.
I didn't know it'd be so hard.
Well, at least you tried your best for him.
By the way, how'd you find out about this whole thing?
That part doesn't matter.
Last month, I was passing by a dojo.
There have been lots of stories about murders lately, and I was kinda creeped out.
So I thought maybe I should learn to fight.
That's when I met Suwen, the owner of the dojo.
Hello, miss.
Looking to learn?
Huh?
Come in and have a seat if you're interested.
Or if you simply want to chat, I'm all ears.
Year after year, he's fought the father of the woman he loves.
But he always fails.
The dad wanted someone from a martial arts family as a son-in-law.
That's why this client trained so hard and opened his own dojo.
Everyone laughed at him and her family, saying they were all stubborn.
That things like this didn't matter nowadays.
Go back inside.
We've seen the last of your failed suitor.
That poor fool.
He never should have challenged me.
And the one who should have proved himself...
Master, please stop.
I surrender.
I can't.
Gave up a long time ago.
Hey, uh...
Isn't this against your sacred rules?
Don't worry.
I'll keep us in line.
Oh, Jan!
I've come to bury you!
I've devoted myself to this.
Living each day by a disciplined diet.
Sacrificing my time and body.
Training like a madman.
But I never realized how strong her father was.
I can't defeat him.
Nor will I outlive him.
And as he has passed, the stairs got harder to climb.
Hold on.
You two have been in love forever.
Why do you even need his approval?
I still persevere.
Because I promised my Ooyang a proper marriage.
I refuse to let her down.
I have a plan.
You want to hear it?
Su-Wen.
Next year, can we fight at the bottom?
My blessing.
Why didn't you let go sooner?
Even my grandchild is a reputable fighter now.
And yet this man couldn't defeat me.
How was I supposed to approve of him, to accept his weakness?
So, what's the hardest thing about love?
People have asked that question for a long, long time.
And now?
Why don't you throw that antique in the trash?
Here, give it to me!
I think I finally know the answer.
I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
Is everything going to happen now?
I'm so sad to see you in the past.
I don't know why the answer has left too much.
猜疑着的人都谢谢出现过
Thank you.